Steven D Kelley: Hello everyone.
Welcome to the show. My name is
Steven D Kelley. This is the
Steven D Kelley show.
It's Thursday, once again, it's
November 13. Oh, I gotta set the
microphone down, getting
the noises.
It's November 13. 1113,
it's now 6:03pm. 2025
title, The Tonight Show. This
just came to me a little while
ago. I love how that always
happens, is sins of a father,
and that'll make more sense as
we go along.
And I'd like to say that I'm
excited to be here, but I can
never tell anymore if it's
excitement or anger, or what a
combination thereof and and I'll
tell you sometimes stuff hits me
that, you know, I already knew,
but when it hits me in the face
with like, you know that proof
thing that that give me a link,
thing that people are always
asking for. Like, there it is.
There it is in writing. There's
the smoking gun, there's the
proof. There's the footprints,
the fingerprints, whatever it is
that you need to prove things.
There it is. Now,
you know, honestly,
I've, I've had the, I don't know
if you want to call it a curse
of the blessing of kind of
knowing stuff that I'm not
supposed to know. I have no
reason to know. I just know, and
I guess that's what, that's what
being psychic is all about, is
that you just know stuff, and
you don't really have any reason
to know it. And sometimes you
know stuff, and you try to share
that with people, and it really
bothers those people, until, of
course, it comes out to be true.
You know, if you know what I
mean, I mean I'm talking petty
stuff, you know, like
relationships at home and bad
decisions people are going to
make, you say, Oh, you better
not do that, you know. And then,
of course, it's like, I used to
have a saying, it sucks being
right all the time,
but I'll tell you this, this
Getty stuff though, this whole
saving the world business, and
this whole fighting against
satanist and all that about,
first of all, before I go any
further, shout out to the guys
over there in tin hat
tin foil hat,
not the small not to be confused
with the small hat gang, but the
tin foil hat gang. No,
so where was I? Oh yeah, the
fighting these satanist stuff.
You know, I broke my program a
long time ago. I'll tell you
that. But
the thing is, is that, uh,
well,
when the time comes, and I think
it's coming really soon,
because, like I said, the
smoking guns are starting to be
uncovered. And, you know, like
the Epstein thing and the Trump,
the Trump pedophilia thing and
the Intertel mafia thing. It's
just not going away. And of
course, then there's the whole
Occupy the Getty thing and
Gordon Getty, and it's been
difficult to tie all this stuff
in together. And of course, when
you're psychic, you don't really
need to, because you already
know it's like, it's like,
connecting all the dots. I don't
need to connect all the dots. I
already know where all the dots
go. I've seen I've know the
path. It's kind of like
electricity. When you understand
Saturn, and you understand the
true nature of electricity, you
understand it. It already knows
where it's going a long time
before it travels down the wire,
crazy stuff. But that's way
beyond the scope of normal
humans, much like this whole
business with this whole saving
the world crap and this whole
corrupting the world crap. And,
you know, Satanism in general,
we like to think we understand
it, but we don't. And I'll tell
you, me personally, even though
I have all this personal
experience and insight, and, you
know, changing programming,
you know, actual, actual hands
on involvement. It still took me
a long time to figure a lot of
things out. Hell, it took me
five years to figure out that
the CIA that I was working for
was actually the NSA, but was
actually the NSA, the Oliver
North gang. It took me another
20 years to figure out it was
intertel and all that business
and and the whole Don Nixon,
Robert Vesco mafia business. I
mean, my God, just figuring out
it was all mafia took a long
time, and basically what that
tells me is that
I'm 20 years behind them.
It takes me a little while
to connect my dots, to figure
out what's going on that I'm
sharing with you, this stuff I'm
sharing with you about the Getty
and everything like that. That
took me a while to put it
together. And as I've been
traveling down this path now for
a good 20 something years, or
whatever it is, since I you
know, from 1990 or 2000 whenever
you want us consider it having
started 87 if you want to go
back to that far. But I guess it
got, it got really, you know,
Oliver North stuff that was 2000
you know, and, or no, was that?
No, that was 1990 then, of
course, the Getty stuff was like
2000 so it's like, when do you
want? It was been real the whole
time.
Yeah, but even then I was naive,
and I was just floundering in
there, like some sort of,
well average guy, like I like to
claim to be
immersed in this underworld of
wicked activity. And it took,
it's constantly taking me this
long to understand it, but I
realize now,
after so many years of trying to
share this information with you
guys and trying to get you guys
to respond and trying to make
changes, you know, positive
changes, with using based on the
stuff that I'm trying to share
with you, I realize that you're
like 20 years behind me,
and your best tool that you've
got was good 20 years behind the
enemy. That tells you what's
what we're looking at. It's
probably more like 50 years,
okay, whatever it is that we
know, or we think we know, or
what we're beginning to figure
out, is a good 50 years beyond
what they've been doing. They're
ahead of us that much. And
that's about, right? I mean, in
a typical satanic scenario, like
your typical protocols of the
learned elderness of Zion, type
of policy making, you're looking
at hundreds of years of policy
development. But the humans that
are running our situation on
Earth right now. They operate in
frames of about 50 years, and it
takes us about that long to
figure it out, but, but I'll
tell you, I figured it out.
Okay, this Getty thing. I don't
need to know all the stuff, but
I figured it out. I knew it was
bad this minute. I drove past
the place on the freeway. I knew
it was a big deal, and there was
something seriously wrong with
it. I didn't need the answers. I
just knew. I didn't know why.
Eventually I would learn the why
was because the entire stake of
the world and lives of billions
of people were at stake, and
that this was basically the root
of all Satanism on Earth, as far
as I was concerned. Well, you
know, if you want to consider
the Magna Carta and the throne
of the leaders of the Magna
Carta, you know, important,
sure, little hats Nazis aside, I
don't need to get into all that,
but I do know one thing for
sure. And I do know that from
their own mouth, they told me,
this is the answer. This is
their weak spot. This is how I
personally take them down
forever, and there's nothing
they can do about it to stop me.
And I don't need to know all the
details, but
we can share some of the details
now, before I try to get in
these details, because I want to
get into the latest revelations
coming out that basically
connect.
Gordon, Getty, Epstein and
Trump.
But before I do that, as long as
I don't lose my brain somewhere
between now and that, I just
want to say that I'm I'm
disgusted. I really am
disgusted. It's hard for me to
do this. I mean, let alone my
own personal inconveniences and
and tribulations and dramas and
what have you, and the fact that
I'm so darn tired of life in
general, because I've devoted
the best part of my life to this
mission and given up everything
I've earned and worked so hard
for, including my family,
friends, reputation, etc, and on
and on and on and on, not least
of which was All the money and
worldly conveniences and
material goods. Yeah, that I
gave up. Yeah, all my damn guns.
So hello, hello, you guys. I
know you don't have any idea
what I'm talking about, but
there was a lot of guns and
everything else.
But
it's not the,
you know, I mean, as a warrior,
obviously, I, I that's not the
part that bothers me. Okay,
sure, the the ongoing pain of
having, of the of the loss and
the sacrifices, is forever.
Okay, you can't fix that. You
can't give me back my life and
my family and my youth and my
money and all that stuff. You
just can't do it. My My
children, watching my children
grow up. Can't do that. Okay, so
the only thing I have left, of
course, is defeating this enemy.
And apparently that's
that's probably why it's going
to be successful. They are going
to get defeated.
But beyond the discussed part
before I get into the stuff that
talking about Trump and now
Trump, Trump is a disgusting
person, and apparently Gordon
Getty thinks so too. Gordon
Getty is still alive.
Now,
to preface this, I'll just say
that I was inside of Gordon
Getty's house, and the house
that I was in was the one that
he shared with his mistress, the
Beck woman over there in, I
don't know, some part of La
Hollywood area, ritzy, ritzy
part, I'm sure. But either way,
when his
second marriage became public.
They vacated the premises and
left it vacant. And I was led to
it by somebody who basically
discovered it with psychics kill
because we did. It's not the
sort of thing they advertised.
But anyway, she stumbled upon
it, and she said, Hey, let's go
check this house out. low and
behold, it was Gordon Getty's
fucking house.
Neither one of us had a clue
anyway, so while I was in there,
rummaging through what was left
behind, which was pretty much
everything,
I mean a lot.
Kendalle, if you're listening,
I've got some of your stuff. I
got one of your your photos of
your dad with with Judge Newsom
at Yosemite, and I swear I want
to pick up some of your little
childhood mementos, like your
little pottery pop projects you
made at school and stuff. There
was this one little clay box I
saw that I thought was cool. I
wanted to share it. Save it for
you, because I'm sure it was you
regret having to leave that
stuff behind, and I feel sorry
for you. But
while I was rummaging through
Gordon Getty's house, I didn't
just find empty coke bottles and
snuff porn and the craziest ass
video, VHS videos. You can
imagine that he was probably
having weird, kinky sex to one
on coke. Seriously, the guy was
sick, if you just judging by the
porn the videos that he left
behind. But he left behind a lot
of documents, tons and tons and
tons of documents, paperwork
everywhere. Okay? And I read
some of this paperwork. A lot of
it
was stuff that he sent out to so
called world leaders, Gordon
Getty, from the desk of Gordon
Getty type stuff, talking to
some president of such and such,
Premier of this and that,
offering some advice on some
sort of geopolitical situation.
You're thinking, What the hell
is Gordon Getty offering advice
these people about anything, and
usually this stuff was really
bizarre, complex, socio
political, human crap. Okay,
very strange half the time. And
I think again, what the hell is
this Gordon Getty? Think he is?
And why in the hell would these
people listen to him?
Never made sense to me.
But, you know, at the time, I
didn't understand the club.
Okay, I didn't understand the
club. So why would I understand
that?
Well, something came out
as a result of a
House committee. No, I don't
know the details, because I know
everything in Washington is
bullshit. And before I go any
further, I want to say something
that I know,
Ed, this is kind of for you, but
I just want to say to all of you
out there that are working for
this government, this so called
government,
it's nothing more than a mafia
right now, whatever the
institution was, it no longer
is, because it has been usurped
by mafia powers and it is no
longer valid, and your laws and
your constitution, everything
else have been usurped. You
don't just fuck the Queen and
make Rothschild babies and claim
the throne in this country. No,
it doesn't work like that. You
can take your mafia shit and
shove it up your ass. But the
point is, speaking of ass,
you're going to be kissing a lot
of it. Because all of you
motherfuckers, when you don't
die, when you don't get your
head cut off, and your time is
coming soon, you're going to be
kissing my ass in a serious
fashion, motherfuckers,
I can guarantee you that.
So you need to think twice about
what you do in the future,
because if I have the FBI, next
time I have the FBI pussies show
up at my door to try to
intimidate me,
I would love to see them try to
do something it doesn't fucking
matter anymore, because you know
what I knew before anybody. I
know your whole damn fucking
game. There's nothing you can
do. I know every single fucking
thing I've got dirt on every
single motherfucking one of you.
And the damn emails and texts
and connections are starting to
come out now. Anyway, here's
this one that just came out.
Now, of course, the media is
going to try to spin it in such
a way that they can make it
political. Okay, it's kind of
like be the way Donald Trump has
been protecting himself against
the Epstein files coming out
saying now the, of course, the
Democrats are saying that the
GOP means the guardians of
pedophilia, you know, which is
a, course, a connection to the
Guardians of the Galaxy movie.
So guardians of pedophilia? Yes,
they're all the guardians of
pedophilia. Everything they do
right now isn't just about
genocide and promoting Israel,
which of course, has a lot to do
with pedophilia and stealing oil
and making money and putting
gold all over the White House
and tearing down the east wing.
No, no,
It's about defending themselves
against Epstein. Now, now here's
the thing, and I've been trying
to tell you guys this for a long
time, but Trump is a little fish
in this game. Sure. He was a big
shot with the Intertel Mafia. He
was the man that.
Man there was a CEO of Resorts
International after Robert Vesco
died, and you would think that
would put him right up there
with Robert Vesco. Apparently,
it was not, because, apparently
there is another man who is the
real granddaddy of this shit, as
I've been trying to tell you for
all this time, and his name is
Gordon fucking Getty.
Now the Jewish Nazi, of course,
is Alan Dershowitz. Now, to
understand the concept of Jewish
Nazi, of course, you have to
understand the Chabad Jews. And
I've been trying to get these
people through, through your
head that these mafioso people
are Jewish Nazis, this Epstein
clown, this Alan Dershowitz guy,
this is the Jewish Nazi. The
same thing the Gordon Getty.
They're all really Jewish Nazis.
So they're talking about their
own club here, Jewish Nazi club,
and they're saying that Donald
Trump is a narcissistic
psychopath. Okay, like it's
known this is high importance to
these guys. So let me see. What
else is there? Okay, here it is.
Let me see if I can give you the
course I've got the media, of
course, they're going to try to
reword this. They go in messages
obtained by a House committee.
Epstein corresponded with Robert
Trivers, an American
evolutionary biologist, a
eugenicist, about a theory put
forward by Gordon Getty, an
influential businessman, not
just an influential businessman,
but their godfather, their
spiritual leader, that Mr. Trump
is quote psychopath or sociopath
or malignant narcissist, and
must be opposed with full force
on that basis, unquote.
So accordingly, Jeffrey Epstein
responds, and supposedly he's
responding to Robert Trivers,
and he says, I think you might
be missing the benefit of. Of
the psychopath to the group. He
is the defender, easily
sacrificed, but strikes fear in
the heart of other tribes. They
are needed as best warriors. Now
to understand this, you have to
understand the Old Testament.
You have to read the Old
Testament, because if you
understand that, you'll know
that the Israelites had a a long
history of making a low life
criminal their leader, because
they figured that this low life
criminal would scare the shit
out of their enemies and do the
unspeakable things that needed
to be done to defend them.
There's a long history of this
sort of thing, so you might be
missing the benefit of the
psychopath to the group. So in
other words, it's a group. They
are all part of a group, right
there. It says that Jeffrey
Epstein, this other guy, this
eugenicist, these Jewish Nazis
with Gordon Getty, is their
godfather. Leader. Is a group, a
very strange group that, yes,
what I found out should not just
be Zionist Jews, but Nazis,
through and through, at the same
time, operating side by side,
dual polarities, like we
discussed in the last show. So
he's has a benefit, because he's
a defender. He's defending them
from their stuff. He will, He
will kill everybody to defend
the world from the truth about
Epstein. And he's easily
sacrificed. They can toss him
under the bus anytime they want,
because they control him. They
have dirt on him. Epstein has
anything he needs to bring him
down. Mossad Netanyahu has
everything they need to be bring
him down. He says so right here
in 20 fucking 12 or whatever the
hell it is. But he strikes fear
in the heart of other tribes,
other tribes. There's that tribe
bullshit mentality. Who are
they? They are the tribe. They
are still fighting other tribes,
like the amaleks. Us, the ones
they want to genocide. We are
just another tribe that their
God says should be genocided,
and they need Trump as their
best lawyer. They need that a
disgusting piece of shit, Trump.
I didn't even want to do a show
because I'm so sick of saying
how disgusting Trump is and how
disgusted I am that so many
people still trust him, so many
people still listen to him. He's
a fucking pedophile. He's
committed incest. He is a coke
head. He does everything
possible you could fucking
imagine. He killed little boys
and little girls. He's a
horrible person. His entire
business empire is based on lies
and deception, money laundering,
deceit, Mafia activity. He
didn't make anything. He is
nothing but added value. And the
only thing he made was those
buildings, and he had to tear
down better structures to make
those things. And he used mafia
to make it, and he buried his
victims in the foundation with
the cement and concrete poured
by the mafia, the same mafia
that he was a part of. And yet
he runs our government, and yet
we have Kash Patel telling
people this so called pussy Kash
Patel that will send fucking FBI
to my door because of the
treasonous things I'm saying
about this bullshit mafia
fucking country, fuck Israel.
He's actually suing some
YouTuber, supposedly, or
whatever, because he was calling
his honey pot girlfriend,
Mossad. Yet he didn't even call
the girlfriend, Mossad.
Apparently, the lawsuit says
that he didn't even say that. He
said that he was just basically
saying bad things about Israel.
So now saying bad things about
Israel means that fucking Kash
Patel is going to sue you for 5
million fucking dollars. It's
fucking clown. World, if you're
not disgusted, there's something
wrong with you, if you're taking
their fucking money in the form
of a paycheck, and look, you're
looking the other way, and
you're so worried about your own
reputation and your mortgage and
your food and your children and
your livelihood, if you're so
worried about it that you will
continue to do whatever the fuck
needs to be done just to get by
so they don't fucking take all
your money away like they're
going to do to everybody in a
heartbeat as soon as our digital
ID system becomes worldwide. My
God, everything I've said is
correct, everything a photograph
of Jeffrey Epstein came out of
him in Africa, in Côte d'Ivoire,
whatever it is, one of those
Western African countries
hotbeds. And he was there
because he was helping them
install a system to track and
control everybody. Basically a
Palantir. He was using this war
zone and this undemocratic
dictatorship to install and test
hardware and software that the
CIA developed with Elon Musk
with with asshole Peter Thiel,
with Jeffrey Epstein, with
Gordon Getty, with the whole
fucking gang, and they tested it
back there. What more do you
fucking need? There's Palantir,
way back when, there's Elon,
there's there's fucking Larry
Ellison, there's Microsoft.
There's every single one of
them, every single one of them
connected to Epstein, why did
they go there not just to fuck
children? Fucking children was
the bonus. They went there to
talk about their world
domination and their satanic
club that they belonged in.
That's why they were there. They
were implementing policy, long
term strategic policy designed
to control and implement your
death, but you don't have to go
along with it. You could help
me. You could stop fucking with
me. You can make this your life.
You know I'm sorry if you don't
like my attitude, I'm sorry to
all the people that think I'm
just a fucking grumpy, angry old
fucking man, maybe I fucking AM.
If you lost everything, if you
gave up everything for a bunch
of ungrateful retards. And you
know what I do? Appreciate all
of you that have been helping me
so much. And yes, we've actually
did have a few new people
joining the group. Hell, we're
up to, what is it? 7515 or
something. Last time I looked
up, we've looked at it, we we've
gone up over 50 or something
like that. So I know something's
going on. My God, maybe the fact
that they're actually saying
Gordon Getty his name in the
fucking Washington that should
give you a clue, people, that
this shit is coming down, and
ultimately it's all going to
lead back to the one weak link,
the weak link in the House of
Cards, as I like to say with my
mixed metaphors. Yep, that's my
original Getty mixed metaphor,
right there. Weak link in the
House of Cards. Anyway, people,
I'm disgusted, yeah? People I
want to give up. Yeah, I've had
enough of it. What more can I
lose? You know, apparently I
can't even lose my life, but I
gotta be bitter. I'd love to,
well, I'm getting a little bit
of satisfaction. But, you know,
this, this revenge stuff? No,
this, this is not satisfying to
me. Yeah, sure. I mean, when I,
when I read this message between
Gordon Getty, you know,
indirectly, and Jeffrey Epstein
and and talking about Donald
Trump being a sociopath, and
referring to them all as being a
member of a big club, a tribe.
It's like when George Carlin
said, it's a big club, and you
ain't in it. You know what? It's
a big tribe, and you ain't in
it. Okay? Now, those of you that
were born in the tribe, like I
try to tell you all, it's not
everyone in the tribe that's
responsible. It's just like the
CIA. There's good, conscientious
people. The CIA,
there's good, conscientious
police officers. They're all
over the place. Laura sent me
fucking food. I got a I got a
roast in there. I don't know how
many pounds. It's pretty big.
We're gonna cook it up tomorrow
night. Jose's gonna come over
here, beef for days anyway, and
lots of other fun stuff. The
ginger, you sent me a bunch of
ginger. I don't know what to get
to with that, but I'll figure
something else, something out
that's ginger for a year. I
mean, hell anyway, sorry for the
dog. Version. Did I mention I
was disgusted people? Seriously,
it's amazing I even have
anything to talk to you about,
but I don't like repeating
myself. I really don't, and I
certainly don't write this stuff
down. I don't prepare speeches
for you. I don't prepare shows.
It's not like I'm having some
guests that's going to come here
and talk and I'm going to ask
questions. Mm, questions. Give
me a list of the questions you
want me to ask you before you
get here. I mean, come on, man,
like this information here about
Epstein and and Donald Trump,
his, his, I mean, come on. The
Club says Donald Trump's a
psychopath, but he's a useful
psychopath that they can throw
under the bus because they've
got dirt on him, and he
intimidates everybody, you know,
like I said, he's all full of
bluster. He's all full of
bluster. But you know what that
facade is failing away. My God,
it's so bad. It's so bad. Can I?
You know, seriously, I I don't.
I didn't want to do a show
tonight. Seriously, I mentioned
that I really didn't want to do
a show. I figure if I do do a
show, it's just gonna be short
because I'm like, I said, I'm so
disgusted. But I do need to get
this information out. And the
only thing that's really
beneficial about all of this is
that the very fact that this did
come out, even though the media
is trying to distort it and try
to make it look like somehow
Gordon Getty is calling Trump a
psychopath. Is a good thing, you
know, kind of like saying only
Republicans now are defending
the pedophiles. Remember when it
was the other way around? Huh?
When, when Obama was in office
and Hillary was the big
pedophile? Now suddenly it's the
hits the Republicans. Seriously,
people, have you fallen for this
shit? You fucking retarded. And
this disgusts me, and I've had
enough of it anyway. All right,
once again, if you, if you do
want to, I, you know, I don't
even know where the watch this
video, because I don't put these
things up, and Cynthia isn't
putting them up anymore because
she's upset about my my Steven D
Kelly soap opera show, and I
hope she'll get over it, but
hope she'll get back on the
mission. Because obviously, I'm
not the mission. I'm sorry. You
know I'm I like Rambo said.
Rambo actually told me to use
whatever I have to try to get
people motivated. You know,
Rambo said, he goes. He says, My
I mean, I'm not following his
instructions very well. I try to
a little bit. But he said, work
out. Obviously. Said, workout.
I'm not doing that. Obviously I
should be, but I'm not. He said
to grow my beard out. He said,
to wear black clothing. Wear
only black clothing. I do that
anyway. I'm not right. I don't
grow my beard out, but. But he
thought if I grew my beard out,
wore black clothing and got all
steadily worked out, I guess I'd
look like Dan Bilzerian, but
maybe a little taller than Dan
Bilzerian, but. But the idea
that was that this was supposed
to help me influence people to
the cause. And the idea was it
was supposed to make all the men
want to be my friends, and all
the women want to be my special
friend. That's just how it is.
That's the dynamics of the human
human nature. What I found
actually, is that when I'm most
effective is when I have a
female counterpart, you know, a
complimentary female
counterpart, who will actually
balance that energy out. Because
I In an ideal situation, the
power couple are both desirable,
if you will. I mean the men all
want the woman, the women all
want the man that that's the
ultimate power couple. The men
all want to be friends with the
man, and the women all want to
be friends with a woman. You
know, it's, it's, that's the
ultimate power couple. I could
think of some throughout
history, but Anthony and
Cleopatra, there you go. There's
a power couple. But anyway, so,
yeah, to achieve that in life is
certainly a good thing if you're
trying to do a mission like
this. But unfortunately, I'm I'm
doing it the best I can with
what I have, and I'm
appreciative of all you guys's
efforts. You know, seriously,
the memes and stuff, people
still ask me. Jones sent me
messages. Who does your videos?
Well, I do my videos, such as
they are, but it's up to other
people to post these things. You
know, if you want to help this
mission and you don't know what
to do, start a YouTube page. I
mean, if you put my stuff on
YouTube, chances are they'll cut
cut it off. I mean, my God, you
imagine I'd probably have 15
million viewers or subscribers
if I wasn't censored. But
anyway, I am censored and I am
cut off. But if, but they can't
stop us all. So if a million of
you all open up pages on rumble
and YouTube and Brighton or
whatever, and you saturate the
place with these silly videos. I
mean, I know you got which ones
apart. I just want to post the
important ones. No, you got to
post them all. You got to
archive it all. All because I
can't do it. As soon as I do it,
they'll shut it down. I'm too
busy trying to create the
content. I can't worry about
producing it and distributing
it. I need your help anyway,
again, thanks to all the people
that are working so hard in the
group, because obviously I can't
do it alone. And you're the
reason why so many people know
about this stuff and why we're
getting to where we are. There's
one thing, though, I want to
leave you with. I don't worry we
got a long ways to go, but one
of the things that Trump's doing
right now that I obviously I'm
extremely disgusted about,
because, as I mentioned
previously, there's three things
in my life that I need, that are
being slowly taken away from me.
Let me see. Can you remember
what they are? One of them's
food, one of them sex. What's
the other one? Pot? Well, Trump,
Trump, Trump. Trump wants to
make THC illegal. What the THC
illegal? It just, it's, it's
booming. Why? What the hell. But
they're not saying earlier.
They're calling it hemp product.
We want to make hemp product
legal. Hemp products. What do
you want to do? A hemp product
is a rope. It's a canvas sale,
it's a bag. It's canvas. That's,
that's a hemp product. We don't
smoke hemp products. Hemp is
fiber, okay? The bud is the
flower. It's not hemp flower.
Not smoking hemp flower. We're
smoking cannabis sativa. It's
not marijuana. It's not hemp.
It's Cannabis sativa, the
psychoactive ingredient, the
active ingredient, which cures
cancer. Fucking shit. It's,
there's a patent on it, it cures
cancer. Holy shit, it's THC. Now
there are variations of THC, and
because of the recent
legalization, the biology and
the work that's being done with
the different strains they're
they're coming up with
incredible products, you know,
isolating terpenes and getting,
you know, analyze, you know,
CBD, CBD oils and what have you.
I mean, my God, if you have a
brain seizure, you take CBD. I'm
serious, that's how you stop a
brain seizure. See, I don't know
anything else to tell you. Hell,
I had a dog was having brain
seizures. She died, of course,
but I did would do anything to
try to relieve some of the agony
that dog was going through. And
the only thing that would help
was CBD. I gave it to our 5000
milligram dosages, concentrated
stuff. I would do it again in a
heartbeat. Anyway. The point is,
is that this is real, live
medicine. And of course, the
pharmaceutical industry doesn't
like this, because, yes, it's
become a multi billion hell,
just the edibles alone, the
product you know, the products
that are being sold food,
products that are being sold
here in California that have a
THC, additives, you know, made
from concentrates, are it's a
billion dollar industry. It's
fast approaching a multi billion
dollar industry and and we
always wondered how the
monsantos and the crafts and
these big, giant food
conglomerates, these agro
industry giants, were going to
keep up with these, these little
growers that are operating in
warehouses all over the country,
at least the state here. Well
anyway, what are they doing?
They're adding billions of
dollars to the state's economy.
And of course, California, it's
a big it's a big deal. And all
the other states will get on,
get in on it. And they are. Here
comes Trump. I mean seriously,
Trump, are you fucking senile?
What's the real reason for doing
this? Well, obviously, the
pharmaceutical companies are in
trouble
with their mRNA drugs and their
inability to try to inflict
covid upon everybody. That was a
big failure. And of course, the
2040, whatever it is, trillion
dollars of debt that the United
States owes it goes to directly
to supporting the pharmaceutical
bullshit, which, of course, is
under the control of the mafias.
It's just one branch of the
mafia, you know, add in the
stock market, banking,
insurance, and, of course,
Hollywood, you know, you've that
kind of thing, the media empire.
Those are the branches of what
controls us, the mafia. But
anyway, so, yeah,
pharmaceuticals are shitting
their pants. But you know, what
is the real reason when they're
really worried about this pot?
Well, you know, here's the
thing, as I said in the last
show, the little hats are
freaking out because the. Uh,
you know, the kingdom of little
hats. It depends on controlling
people and keeping them stupid
and keeping them programmed, and
they work really hard to do this
to everybody from a really
early, early stage. Now, there
is one thing that breaks
programming. And if you've ever
talked to anybody who was MK
Ultra or this sort of thing, or,
you know, Mylab military
abduction, they will tell you
that the programming that they
subject you to, which is usually
psychotropic drugs and stuff
like that, is defeated with pot
THC defeats it ends it stops it.
It's like a light switch. The
brain goes, Wait a minute. Why
in the hell did I believe all
that bullshit for all those
years? What in the hell was that
all about? It's very confusing.
It's kind of like when you die
and you spent three years in
darkness, and during that time,
you're getting downloaded the
entire Akashic records, and that
whole time, you're going, what
the fuck you know, kind of like
I said I was doing when I
realized that 20 years they've
been doing this shit right in
front of my face. I'm just now
figuring it out, and I'm trying
to share it with you guys to
give you a 20 year head start,
and it's only going to happen if
you actually listen to me, but I
I first got exposed to pot in
when I was, like 13 years old.
And I know I don't recommend
this, because pot does have
estrogen promotion, and that's
not good for young men. You
know, when they're growing up,
you don't want to be giving boys
anything has anything to do with
estrogen. It's like soy. Don't
give your children your male
children soy. Give it to your
girls. But no, in fact, you're
going to give anything to your
boys. Give them beef, red beef.
It's got male hormone in it.
Okay? Milk, well, milk has
growth hormone, but it's bovine
growth hormone, but it over
chicken has a lot of female
estrogen in it anyway. Point is,
is that when I was 13, I was in
Catholic school still, and I
when I got woke up and I'm like,
oh my god, suddenly none of it
made sense. Did not fit in
anymore. And then I went to
public school, and guess what?
It didn't make sense there
either everything. I had to redo
everything. I mean, that's when
it really started, when you
started questioning everything,
when you start when I that's
when I realized that everybody
was really kind of stupid. I
realized my teachers were
stupid. I realized a lot of
things, you know, I mean, some
things it took a long time to
realize, like, like, all my
female teachers were, I wouldn't
say they're molested me. Well,
let's just say they, mostly,
most of them, loved me when I
was going through the Catholic
school. I mean, even the nuns,
the nuns would have me sitting
on their lap. But the only
teacher that didn't like me was
my first grade teacher, and she
was a lesbian, but her partner
was my second grade teacher, and
she did like me. So hey, what
can I say? Right? I guess one
was Butch and the other one was
not so Butch and the not so
Butch liked me. So funny how
that stuff works anyway. Such is
life. Alright, listen, guys, I
do again, like I said, want to
thank all you people that helped
me with the mission and people
are trying to help me. Trying to
help me, give me motivation to
hang in there, you know, like
eating and stuff. Yeah, eating
is important. And yeah, I'm
trying to eat and blah, blah,
blah. And, yeah, it is nice
having food around, although I
don't have any idea what I'm
going to do with all that
ginger, Laura, but you'll have
to send me some recipes. But if
you'd want to help me out. Of
course, financially, it's Yahoo
or not Yahoo, but PayPal. PayPal
is stevenkelley714@yahoo.com.
That's s, t, e, v, e, n, k, e,
l, l, e, y, 7, 1, 4@yahoo.com
and you have safe for your
family. And I did get a couple
donations from a couple people.
I'm not gonna say her name. One
guy sent me, I think it was 10
bucks. Another one sent me 20. I
think just recently, pretty sure
it was 20. I don't think it's
more than that, but anyway, I
try to send thank yous back when
you do that. But sometimes they
make me have to sign in to
PayPal to do it. PayPal makes
me, like, jump through hoops
like, like, send a code to my
cell phone. I don't have a cell
phone. I'm using someone else's
cell phone, just like I'm using
someone else's bank account just
to have a damn PayPal at all.
Okay, so it just be it, be it.
No, don't think that just
because I have a PayPal that
I've got, like, you know, credit
cards and everything else I
don't seriously. I was, I was,
I'm a broke joke. But that
doesn't mean I won't send you
something if you need it, all
right, anyway. So, yeah, help me
out if you can. But of course,
the most thing, helpful thing
that you can do is, like I said,
share these videos. Join the
group. I. Telegram, which is
this, occupy the Getty slash
Steven D Kelley group. And
remember the occupy the Getty
thing. It's not going away. That
slogan, whether you like it or
not, you think, Well, what does
this occupy? The thing that
sounds violent, that's so it
doesn't matter what it sounds
like anymore. What the original
intention of it, what it is, is
our flag. Okay, people, it's our
flag. The reasoning for why that
flag was created may become a
little blurry as time goes on,
but it doesn't matter, because
the point is that this is a flag
that is established and
recognized, and it's only a
matter of time before we are
talked about in a less
disparaging way. It's like if
you ask grok about me right now,
of course, grok has been
reprogrammed so many times you
can't keep up with it, but grok
will tell you that I'm a file
Grok will say, there's no
evidence. There's no evidence.
Everything I say is BS, it's,
it's conspiracy. Never minded
Gordon Getty and Epstein and all
these people are just calling
Donald Trump a psychopath, like
he's a crazy child that they
want to take advantage of who
they do. And yet, you all think
he's fucking wonderful. I can't
believe it's like I said. I'm
disgusted when I see him walking
around the White House with that
gold he has all over the place.
Oh my god. Everybody made a joke
and said that when he became
president, he was going to put
gold all over the place. He
fucking did. What more do you
need? The proof that this is an
ungodly man who mocks us, who
mocks us openly. They don't
care. They just don't care. You
know what they do care about?
They care about the Getty. They
care about me. They care about
what I'm doing. You want to fuck
them over? You want to fuck this
government? Well, if you don't
want to fuck this government,
you might as well become a
pedophile and suck Satan's cock
and be like them. But if you
want that shit to end, if you
want to be a responsible human,
that when you go to heaven, you
don't have to answer to God all
those excuses that you made for
ignoring the things I'm trying
to tell you right now, if you
want to be that person, then
help me out. Find ways to help
me out. Use your skills, use
whatever circle of friends you
have, use whatever resources you
have, find a way. Make an
effort. That's That's all we're
asking. Okay, make an effort.
Serve others, and this is great
way to do it. Okay, I've devoted
my life to it, and I don't
expect you to do that. But if I
don't expect my my contribution,
my sacrifice, to be a waste
either, I already know that I
win this battle, but I'd like it
to be done sooner than later,
and I know that if it takes
longer to do this, and more
people have to suffer before it
gets done, and then I'm flaking
out. So that's why it's
important to me to hang in there
and harass you guys and do
everything I can to try to get
you to help me okay? And that
doesn't mean I'm going to kiss
your ass, and that doesn't mean
I'm looking for you to kiss my
ass. The only people are going
to be kissing my ass are those
people that I spare from having
their heads cut off because they
have been helping enable this
satanic pedophilia for all these
years. And you know who you are?
Just like those FBI
motherfuckers who ran out of my
front yard and me yelling at
them, you are pedophile
enablers, because that is
exactly what they are, Kash,
Patel, all of them, they're all
fucking pedophiles, that tribe,
that club, that Epstein's
talking about pedophiles. If you
can't see that, there's
something wrong with you, if you
think that's okay, there's
something wrong with you. If you
won't help me, there's something
wrong with you. If you think
that you need more proof,
in spite of the fact that
they're even talking about this
connection right now, Getty's
his name is coming up in
connection to Epstein right now.
If that's not good enough for
you, I don't know what more you
need, considering that they
won't even talk about Epstein
yet. Now we've got Getty's name
connected to Epstein, with
Epstein calling it a big club,
with Getty being the patriarch
figure, my God, people, it's
right in front of your face.
Someday, you're going to look
back on everything I've been
saying for all these years. You
know, fucking a it was in front
of our face all that time, and
it was, and that's my job, is
making sure that it is. That's
all I can do. And I'd like to
think that I'm doing my job. And
I'd like to think that maybe,
maybe I've done my job good
enough to earn my place where it
should be. And to get the hell
off this rock with all my sins
forgiven, God willing, that's
the best any of us could hope
for. Alright, so with that, I'm
just going to remind you again
that my name is Steven D Kelley.
Thank you for listening, you
guys over there, tin foil hat,
if you made it this long, right
on, talk to you later. And guys,
I'm not in your group to sell
the page. I'm in there because
you can talk shit and we can
talk shit. Nobody gets butt
hurt. It's like, nice not having
an admin, huh? On my group, you
can't do that anyway. So that's
why it's nice. If you wonder why
I'm there and what, what, what
I'm doing, that's, that's why
I'm there. It's, it's for you
guys. It's because we all harass
each other. Anyway, such is life
right now, right? We're in the
mean wars in the kingdom of the
little hats, right? Anyway,
folks, once again, my name is
Steven D Kelley, and this is the
Steven D Kelley show, and we are
truth, cat radio, the one and
only. And God, I'll tell you,
Mr. Kitten, I don't know. He's
getting old. He's like me. We're
both getting old and skinny, and
I just scares the shit out of me
people. I don't like thinking
about mortality. I'll tell you
one thing about it. I hope you
guys can scrape enough money
together to get me buried.
Seriously, I don't want to get
cremated. End up in a box on my
side. I want to be buried. I
want to have the ashes of my
kitty cats with me, and I have a
stuffed rabbit from, you know,
when I was like, what five I'd
like to have that with me sits
next to my bed. You know, of
course, whatever my Rolex,
whatever, you can keep that and
give it to someone. I'll have a
giveaway my meager possessions.
But seriously, people, right.
Okay, do you understand I think
about things like that. Oh, my
dinner's here. Alright, once
again, my name is Steven Kelley.
This is Steven D Kelley show we
are Truth Cat Radio,
www.truthcatradio.com, thank you
so much for listening. Good
night. God bless. Adios. I Adios
and goodbye bye.